One thing about that Cory Booker, if you putting together a dodgeball team, y'all need to get that light-skinned Negro up on now.
I feel like the opposition needs to be fuck, no, across the board.
What do you have to say about the capitulation that you participated in and where the Democratic Party is right now?
And we have a really good way of holding up these purity tests.
That's such bullshit. It's not a purity test.
It's a, are we in this fight?
We hear you, like when you did your 25-hour speech, I was like, go, Cory.
And then there's a photo shoot with you with Benjamin Netanyahu.
And I was just like, what in the actual?
I'm sorry. I have real problems with Benjamin Netanyahu.
Outrageous things that he's doing.
The way you fight for those things is you sit down face-to-face with somebody.
I have disagreements with a lot of people.
Look, I'm one of a handful of people that don't take corporate PAC money.
I don't understand my Democratic Party.
What about APAC money? You take APAC money, don't you?
That's a minuscule percentage of my resources.
I raised like 800,000.
Yeah, but that's a lifetime number.
So profoundly disappointed with the leadership, like, for example, your colleague Chuck Schumer.
Why do I feel so disappointed with the federal leadership when I see like Gavin Newsom, J.B. Pritzker?
They're out there fighting every day and I just, I see a vacuum.
Okay, so I, and you say Chuck Schumer this, Chuck Schumer this.
I'm telling you right now, most people in my state do not know who Chuck Schumer is.
Right.
They don't.
They can't name him.
They can't name Hakeem Jeffries.
Because the way he be, when he's being asked very clear and direct questions.
Man.